in your life you want to achieve all
your dreams a home for your family a
secure future for your children a
vacation abroad to celebrate a milestone
and so on so to achieve each of our
dreams it is important to have a plan to
help you build a saving scopus while
also providing financial protection for
the family in case of an unfortunate
event
presenting ICICI proof future perfect an
ideal savings and protection oriented
plan that provides Savings in the form
of a lump sum on maturity along with
financial protection for you and your
family
this plan provides savings with the
comfort of guarantee
you will receive a guaranteed maturity
benefit which is a guaranteed lump sum
payable at the policy's maturity get
guaranteed additions these are accrued
as a percentage of annualized premiums
not only that it also provides the
prospects to grow your wealth through
bonuses you can Osteo maturity Corpus
through revisionary bonuses which may be
declared throughout the policy term and
receive a terminal bonus if any at the
end of the policy term the plan also has
the flexibility to choose premium
payment term
premium payment frequency
and policy term as per your need
ICICI prove future perfect also provides
you and your family the security of a
live cover for the entire policy term
what's more this plan will provide you
with tax advantages on premiums paid and
benefits received now let's see how this
plan works say you are a 35 year old
male and you decide to invest in ICICI
proof future perfect you choose a
premium payment term of 10 years and a
policy term of 20 years and you pay 30
000 rupees as an annual premium at the
end of the policy term you are likely to
receive a maturity benefit of 7.04 lakh
Rupees at an ARR of eight percent which
includes a guaranteed maturity benefit
of 2 lakh 29 050 rupees
accrued guaranteed additions of 82 500
rupees vested revisionary bonuses of 1
lakh 28
385 rupees and a terminal bonus of 2
lakh 64 200 and 71 Rupees at 4 percent
ARR the maturity benefit will be 4.27
lakh rupees in case of an unfortunate
incident the nominee gets the life cover
what are you waiting for to secure your
dreams invest in ICICI proof future
perfect plan today
foreign
[Music]